Guide to the Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 4
Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 4
- Box: 70, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 33: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 34: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 35: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.5:no.120
  - Item 36: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 37: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 38: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.5:no.121
  - Item 39: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 40: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 41: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.5:no.122
  - Item 42: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 43: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 44: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.5:no.123
  - Item 45: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 46: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 47: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.5:no.124
  - Item 48: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 49: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 50: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.5:no.125
  - Item 51: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 52: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 53: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.5:no.126
  - Item 54: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 55: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 56: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.5:no.127
  - Item 57: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 58: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 59: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.5:no.128
  - Item 60: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 61: Boletin de Noticias, Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 62: Boletin de Noticias, 1968; Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.6:no.133
  - Item 63: Boletin de Noticias, 1968; Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 64: Boletin de Noticias, 1968; Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 65: Boletin de Noticias, 1968; Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.6:no.132
  - Item 66: Boletin de Noticias, 1968; Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 67: Boletin de Noticias, 1968; Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 68: Boletin de Noticias, 1967; Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.5:no.112
  - Item 69: Boletin de Noticias, 1967; Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 70: Boletin de Noticias, 1967; Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.5:no.111
  - Item 71: Boletin de Noticias, 1967; Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 72: Boletin de Noticias, 1968; Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 73: Boletin de Noticias, 1968; Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.6:no.131
  - Item 74: Boletin de Noticias, 1968; Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 75: Boletin de Noticias, 1968; Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 76: Boletin de Noticias, 1968; Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.6:no.129
  - Item 77: Boletin de Noticias, 1968; Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 78: Boletin de Noticias, 1968; Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 79: Boletin de Noticias, 1968; Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: Ano.6:no.130
  - Item 80: Boletin de Noticias, 1968; Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 81: Boletin de Noticias, 1968; Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Item 82: Boletin de Noticias, 1963; Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.38
  - Item 83: Boletin de Noticias, 1963; Publication (Box 70, Folder 2)
- Box: 70, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Metal, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Author: International Metalworkers' Federation
    Notes: v.6:no.5
  - Item 2: Metal, 1965; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.5:no.3
  - Item 3: Metal, 1964; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.4:no.2
  - Item 4: Metal, 1964; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.4:no.3
  - Item 5: Metal, 1964; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.4:no.1
  - Item 6: Metal, 1963; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.3:no.7
  - Item 7: Metal, 1963; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.3:no.6
  - Item 8: Metal, 1963; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.3:no.5
  - Item 9: Metal, 1963; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.3:no.4
  - Item 10: Metal, 1963; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.3:no.3
  - Item 11: Metal, 1963; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.3:no.2
  - Item 12: Metal, 1962; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.2
  - Item 13: Metal, 1967; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.7:no.21
  - Item 14: Metal, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.6
  - Item 15: Metal, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.4
  - Item 16: Metal, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.3
  - Item 17: Metal, 1965; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: 5.5:no.6
  - Item 18: Metal, 1965; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 19: Metal, 1965; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: 5.5:no.5
  - Item 20: Metal, 1964; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.4
  - Item 21: Metal, 1964; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.3
  - Item 22: Metal, 1964; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 23: Metal, 1964; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.1
  - Item 24: Metal, 1963; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.1:no.5
  - Item 25: Metal, 1963; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.1:no.3
  - Item 26: Metal, 1963; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.1:no.2
  - Item 27: Metal, 1963; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.1:no.1
  - Item 28: Metal, 1963; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.1:no.4
  - Item 29: Metal, 1968; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.5
  - Item 30: Metal, 1968; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.4
  - Item 31: Metal, 1968; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.3
  - Item 32: Metal, 1968; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.2
  - Item 33: Metal, 1968; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.8:no.1
  - Item 34: Metal, 1967; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.7:no.5
  - Item 35: Metal, 1967; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.7:no.4
  - Item 36: Metal, 1967; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 37: Metal, 1967; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.7:no.3
  - Item 38: Metal, 1967; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 39: Metal, 1967; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 40: Metal, 1967; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 41: Metal, 1967; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 42: Metal, 1967; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 43: Metal, 1968; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 44: Metal, 1968; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 45: Metal, 1968; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 46: Metal, 1964; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.5
  - Item 47: Metal, 1965; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 48: Metal, 1965; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 49: Metal, 1965; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 50: Metal, 1965; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.3:no.1
  - Item 51: Metal, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 52: Metal, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 53: Metal, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.2
  - Item 54: Metal, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.1
  - Item 55: Metal, 1965; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Item 56: Metal, 1967; Publication (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.7:no.2
- Box: 70, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Heroes de la libertad, 1965; Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
    Author: Carlos Andres Perez
  - Item 2: Revolucion democratica en America latina, 1964; Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
    Author: Romulo Betancourt
  - Item 3: IV Congreso Latinoamericano de Trabajadores -- C.L.A.S.C., Confederacion Latinoamericana de Sindicalistas Cristianos, Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Pablo VI -- La Paz es Posible, 1965; Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Las Naciones Unidas en Venezuela, 1965; Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
    Author: Oficina Central de Informacion
  - Item 6: Letter from Venezuela, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
    Notes: 5
  - Item 7: Letter from Venezuela, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
    Notes: 6
  - Item 8: Letter from Venezuela, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Letter from Venezuela, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
    Notes: 2
  - Item 10: Carta de Venezuela, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
    Notes: 12
  - Item 11: Carta de Venezuela, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
    Notes: 56
  - Item 12: Portada, 1972; Publication (Box 70, Folder 4)
    Notes: 35
- Box: 70, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: La Quinta Rueda: Revista Cultura, 1972; Publication (Box 70, Folder 5)
    Notes: octubre
  - Item 2: La Quinta Rueda: Revista Cultura, 1972; Publication (Box 70, Folder 5)
    Notes: noviembre
  - Item 3: La Quinta Rueda: Revista Cultura, 1972; Publication (Box 70, Folder 5)
    Notes: diciembre
- Box: 70, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Noticiero Interamericano, 1962; Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
    Notes: Ano I
  - Item 2: Noticiero Interamericano, 1962; Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Noticiero Interamericano, 1962; Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Noticiero Interamericano, 1962; Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
    Notes: Ano I:no.3
  - Item 5: Noticiero Interamericano, 1962; Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
    Notes: Ano I:no.4
  - Item 6: Noticiero Interamericano, 1962; Publication (Box 70, Folder 6)
- Box: 70, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Interamerican bulletin, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
    Author: International Federation of Commercial, Clerical, and Technical Employees
    Notes: v.7:no.1
  - Item 2: Interamerican bulletin, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Interamerican bulletin, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Interamerican bulletin, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Interamerican bulletin, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Interamerican bulletin, 1965; Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Interamerican bulletin, 1965; Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Interamerican bulletin, 1965; Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: Interamerican bulletin, 1965; Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.5:no.5
  - Item 10: Interamerican bulletin, 1965; Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.5:no.7
  - Item 11: Interamerican bulletin, 1963; Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.4:no.4
  - Item 12: Interamerican bulletin, 1962; Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: Interamerican bulletin, 1962; Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Item 14: Interamerican bulletin, 1962; Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.3:no.8
  - Item 15: Interamerican bulletin, 1961; Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Item 16: Interamerican bulletin, 1960; Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.1:no.9
  - Item 17: Interamerican bulletin, 1965; Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Item 18: Boletin Interamericano, 1962; Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
    Author: Federacion Internacional de Empleados y Tecnicos
  - Item 19: Boletin Interamericano, 1961; Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Item 20: Boletin Interamericano, 1962; Publication (Box 70, Folder 7)
- Box: 70, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Unity, 1965; Publication (Box 70, Folder 8)
    Author: Postal, Telegraph and Telephone Workers' International
    Notes: v.10:no.1
  - Item 2: Unity, 1965; Publication (Box 70, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.10:no.2
  - Item 3: Unity, 1965; Publication (Box 70, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.10:no.3
  - Item 4: Unity, 1965; Publication (Box 70, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.10:no.4
  - Item 5: Unity, 1965; Publication (Box 70, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.10:no.5
  - Item 6: Unity, 1965; Publication (Box 70, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.10:no.6
  - Item 7: Unity, 1965; Publication (Box 70, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.10:no.7
  - Item 8: Unity, 1965; Publication (Box 70, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.10:no.8
  - Item 9: Unity, 1965; Publication (Box 70, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.10:no.9
  - Item 10: Unity, 1965; Publication (Box 70, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.10:no.10
  - Item 11: Unity, 1965; Publication (Box 70, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.10:no.11
  - Item 12: Unity, 1964; Publication (Box 70, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.9:no.1
  - Item 13: Unity, 1964; Publication (Box 70, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.9:no.2
  - Item 14: Unity, 1964; Publication (Box 70, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.9:no.3
  - Item 15: Unity, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.11:no.1
  - Item 16: Unity, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.11:no.2
  - Item 17: Unity, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.11:no.3
  - Item 18: Unity, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.11:no.4
  - Item 19: Unity, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.11:no.5
  - Item 20: Unity, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.11:no.6
  - Item 21: Unity, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.11:no.7
  - Item 22: Unity, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.11:no.8
  - Item 23: Unity, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.11:no.9
  - Item 24: Unity, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.11:no.10
  - Item 25: Unity, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.11:no.11
  - Item 26: Unity, 1966; Publication (Box 70, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.11:no.12
- Box: 70, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Unity, 1967; Publication (Box 70, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.12:no.1
  - Item 2: Unity, 1967; Publication (Box 70, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.12:no.2
  - Item 3: Unity, 1958; Publication (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Unity, 1959; Publication (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Unity, 1960; Publication (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Unity, 1960; Publication (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: Unity, 1961; Publication (Box 70, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.5:no.1
  - Item 8: Unity, 1961; Publication (Box 70, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.5:no.2
  - Item 9: Unity, 1961; Publication (Box 70, Folder 9)
- Box: 70, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Unity, 1961; Publication (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Unity, 1962; Publication (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Unity, 1962; Publication (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Unity, 1962; Publication (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Unity, 1962; Publication (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Unity, 1962; Publication (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Unity, 1962; Publication (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Unity, 1962; Publication (Box 70, Folder 10)
- Box: 70, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Unity, 1963; Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Unity, 1963; Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Unity, 1963; Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Unity, 1963; Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Unity, 1963; Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Unity, 1963; Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Unity, 1963; Publication (Box 70, Folder 11)
- Box: 70, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Unity, 1964; Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Unity, 1964; Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Unity, 1964; Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Unity, 1964; Publication (Box 70, Folder 12)
- Box: 70, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Chile: Summary of recent events, 1974; Publication (Box 70, Folder 13)
    Author: Embassy of Chile
    Notes: no.264
- Box: 71, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Constitution rules and conditions of membership, Publication (Box 71, Folder 1)
    Author: Barbados Employers' Confederation
- Box: 71, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Monthly Newsletter, 1980; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
    Notes: Dec
  - Item 2: Monthly Newsletter, 1980; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
    Notes: Christmas
  - Item 3: Monthly Newsletter, 1980; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
    Notes: Nov
  - Item 4: Monthly Newsletter, 1980; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
    Notes: Oct
  - Item 5: Monthly Newsletter, 1980; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
    Notes: Sept
  - Item 6: Monthly Newsletter, 1980; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
    Notes: Aug
  - Item 7: Monthly Newsletter, 1980; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
    Notes: July
  - Item 8: Monthly Newsletter, 1980; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
    Notes: June
  - Item 9: Monthly Newsletter, 1980; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
    Notes: May
  - Item 10: Monthly Newsletter, 1980; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
    Notes: April
  - Item 11: Monthly Newsletter, 1980; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
    Notes: March
  - Item 12: Monthly Newsletter, 1980; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
    Notes: Feb
  - Item 13: Monthly Newsletter, 1979; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: Monthly Newsletter, 1979; Publication (Box 71, Folder 2)
- Box: 71, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Monthly Newsletter, 1981; Publication (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Monthly Newsletter, 1981; Publication (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Monthly Newsletter, 1981; Publication (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Monthly Newsletter, 1981; Publication (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Monthly Newsletter, 1981; Publication (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Monthly Newsletter, 1981; Publication (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Monthly Newsletter, 1981; Publication (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Monthly Newsletter, 1981; Publication (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Monthly Newsletter, 1981; Publication (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Monthly Newsletter, 1981; Publication (Box 71, Folder 3)
    Notes: Apri;l
  - Item 11: Monthly Newsletter, 1981; Publication (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Monthly Newsletter, 1981; Publication (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: Monthly Newsletter, 1981; Publication (Box 71, Folder 3)
    Notes: Jan
- Box: 71, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Monthly Newsletter, 1982; Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Monthly Newsletter, 1982; Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Monthly Newsletter, 1982; Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Monthly Newsletter, 1982; Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Monthly Newsletter, 1982; Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Monthly Newsletter, 1982; Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Monthly Newsletter, 1982; Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Monthly Newsletter, 1982; Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Monthly Newsletter, 1982; Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Monthly Newsletter, 1982; Publication (Box 71, Folder 4)
- Box: 71, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Monthly Newsletter, 1983/1984; Publication (Box 71, Folder 5)
    Notes: Dec-Jan
  - Item 2: Monthly Newsletter, 1983; Publication (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Monthly Newsletter, 1983; Publication (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Monthly Newsletter, 1983; Publication (Box 71, Folder 5)
    Notes: July/Aug
  - Item 5: Monthly Newsletter, 1983; Publication (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Monthly Newsletter, 1983; Publication (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Monthly Newsletter, 1983; Publication (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Monthly Newsletter, 1983; Publication (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Monthly Newsletter, 1983; Publication (Box 71, Folder 5)
- Box: 71, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Monthly Newsletter, 1985; Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Monthly Newsletter, 1985; Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
    Notes: Oct/Nov
  - Item 3: Monthly Newsletter, 1985; Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
    Notes: July/Aug/Sept
  - Item 4: Monthly Newsletter, 1985; Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Monthly Newsletter, 1985; Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
    Notes: Mar/Apr/May
  - Item 6: Monthly Newsletter, 1985; Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Monthly Newsletter, 1985; Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Monthly Newsletter, 1984; Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Monthly Newsletter, 1984; Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: Monthly Newsletter, 1984; Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: Monthly Newsletter, 1984; Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: Monthly Newsletter, 1984; Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
    Notes: Aug/Sept
  - Item 13: Monthly Newsletter, 1984; Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: Monthly Newsletter, 1984; Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Item 15: Monthly Newsletter, 1984; Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Item 16: Monthly Newsletter, 1984; Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
    Notes: Apr
  - Item 17: Monthly Newsletter, 1984; Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
    Notes: Mar
  - Item 18: Monthly Newsletter, 1984; Publication (Box 71, Folder 6)
    Notes: Jan/Feb
- Box: 71, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Monthly Newsletter, 1987; Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
    Notes: Nov/Dec
  - Item 2: Monthly Newsletter, 1987; Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
    Notes: Sept/Oct
  - Item 3: Monthly Newsletter, 1987; Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Monthly Newsletter, 1987; Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
    Notes: May/June
  - Item 5: Monthly Newsletter, 1987; Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Monthly Newsletter, 1987; Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Monthly Newsletter, 1987; Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Monthly Newsletter, 1986; Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
    Notes: Oct/Dec
  - Item 9: Monthly Newsletter, 1986; Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
    Notes: July/Sept
  - Item 10: Monthly Newsletter, 1986; Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: Monthly Newsletter, 1986; Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Item 12: Monthly Newsletter, 1986; Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: Monthly Newsletter, 1986; Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Item 14: Monthly Newsletter, 1985/86; Publication (Box 71, Folder 7)
    Notes: Dec/Jan
- Box: 71, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Monthly Newsletter, 1990; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Monthly Newsletter, 1990; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Monthly Newsletter, 1990; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Monthly Newsletter, 1990; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Monthly Newsletter, 1990; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Monthly Newsletter, 1990; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Monthly Newsletter, 1989; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: Monthly Newsletter, 1989; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: Monthly Newsletter, 1989; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: Monthly Newsletter, 1989; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
    Notes: June/July
  - Item 11: Monthly Newsletter, 1989; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
    Notes: April/May
  - Item 12: Monthly Newsletter, 1989; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
    Notes: Jan/Mar
  - Item 13: Monthly Newsletter, 1988; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Item 14: Monthly Newsletter, 1988; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Item 15: Monthly Newsletter, 1988; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
    Notes: July-Nov
  - Item 16: Monthly Newsletter, 1988; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)
    Notes: March/Apr
  - Item 17: Monthly Newsletter, 1988; Publication (Box 71, Folder 8)